<work>
    <title>Work</title>
    <project>
        <infos>
            <title>iPhone X Mockup</title>
            <friendlyName>iphone-x-mockup</friendlyName>
            <description>
                I've been working on this one for quite some time now. Here's a free download for you! The sketch file contains all of the icons, Control Center, and the device — all in vector. If you like it, don't hesitate to share! For commercial use, just ask me!
            </description>
            <actions>
                <label>More info</label>
                <button>
                    <label>Download Sketch file</label>
                </button>
            </actions>
        </infos>
        <image>
            <alt>Multiple iPhone X on a grey background.</alt>
        </image>
    </project>
    <project>
        <infos>
            <title>NCWeather</title>
            <friendlyName>ncweather</friendlyName>
            <description>
                NCWeather is a minimalistic weather widget for iOS 7 and 8. I developed this app/tweak in collaboration with Thomas Finch, a talented developer. You can see more of his work in the section below.
            </description>
            <actions>
                <label>More info</label>
                <button>
                    <label>App Store (Free)</label>
                    <target>target="_blank"</target>
                    <url>https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/ncweather/id937482069?mt=8</url>
                </button>
                <button>
                    <label>Cydia ($0.99)</label>
                    <target>target="_blank"</target>
                    <url>http://cydia.saurik.com/package/org.thebigboss.ncweather/</url>
                </button>
                <button>
                    <label>Thomas Finch's website</label>
                    <target>target="_blank"</target>
                    <url>http://thomasfinch.me/</url>
                </button>
            </actions>
        </infos>
        <image>
            <alt>NCWeather's icons on a dark grey background.</alt>
        </image>
    </project>
    <project>
        <infos>
            <title>MacBook Pro Mockup</title>
            <friendlyName>macbook-pro-mockup</friendlyName>
            <description>
                When the 2016 MacBook Pro was announced, despite the fact that I couldn't afford it at the moment, I wanted to have it immediately. So I jumped in Sketch and made my own device — in vector. If you like it, don't hesitate to share! For commercial use, just ask me!
            </description>
            <actions>
                <label>More info</label>
                <button>
                    <label>Download Sketch file</label>
                </button>
            </actions>
        </infos>
        <image>
            <alt>A MacBook on a grey background.</alt>
        </image>
    </project>
    <project>
        <infos>
            <title>Custom folders for macOS</title>
            <friendlyName>macos-folders</friendlyName>
            <description>
                People say that I am a tidy person. I admit it, I like it when everything is in its own place. That's why I designed this fully editable folder icon pack in Sketch. You too can now make your own folder and use it to sort you files! If you like it, don't hesitate to share! For commercial use, just ask me!
            </description>
            <actions>
                <label>More info</label>
                <button>
                    <label>Download Sketch file</label>
                </button>
            </actions>
        </infos>
        <image>
            <alt>Multiple colored folders on a dark grey background.</alt>
        </image>
    </project>
    <project>
        <infos>
            <title>macOS HDD icons</title>
            <friendlyName>macos-hdd</friendlyName>
            <description>
                For fun, I made all of the icons of each different macOS hard drives in vector. If you like it, don't hesitate to share! For commercial use, just ask me!
            </description>
            <actions>
                <label>More info</label>
                <button>
                    <label>Download Sketch file</label>
                </button>
            </actions>
        </infos>
        <image>
            <alt>Multiple hard drives on a dark grey background.</alt>
        </image>
    </project>
    <project>
        <infos>
            <title>iOS 6 Homescreen</title>
            <friendlyName>ios6-homescreen</friendlyName>
            <description>
                We're way past the iOS 6 era, but making the homescreen in vector was a lot of fun! If you like it, don't hesitate to share! For commercial use, just ask me!
            </description>
            <actions>
                <label>More info</label>
                <button>
                    <label>Download Sketch file</label>
                </button>
            </actions>
        </infos>
        <image>
            <alt>An iPhone with iOS 6 on a grey background.</alt>
        </image>
    </project>
</work>
